<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Pia Vo, and I’m a fourth year biology major at The University of Texas at Austin. I’m also a pre-optometry student and have served as the volunteer coordinator and internal vice president for the Pre-Optometry Professional Society (POPS)! During my free time, you will usually find me outdoors, whether it be biking, hiking trails, or kayaking. Recently, I’ve gotten into baking pastries and painting which has been super therapeutic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python</title>
      <link>/blog/python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python/</guid>
      <description>I was introduced to Python during the last portion of the SDS 348 course, and I learned a couple of neat things that I wanted to share! One such thing is the use of regular expressions and the re.findall() function, which finds all matches and returns them as a list of strings, with each string representing one match.
Here are common regular expressions used in Python:
 Now, let me show you how this can be applied in an example!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pima Indians Diabetes Dataset</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This diabetes dataset was obtained from the Kaggle website, and it provides diagnostic information about female patients at least 21 years of age and of Pima Indian heritage. This dataset contains 768 observations and 9 variables measuring the number of pregnancies the patient has had, plasma glucose concentration, blood pressure in mmHg, tricep skin fold thickness in mm, 2-hr serum insulin level in muU/ml, body mass index in kg/m^2, diabetes pedigree function (scores likelihood of diabetes based on family history), age in years, and whether the patient is diabetic (yes/no).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects  Statistical Modeling  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>